revival I am from ukraine they say to the police
возрождение я из украины говорят милиции
you are from and you are from the crimea and the
вы откуда а вы из крыма да и заклеены
city of kamensky is sealed you are from russian
город каменский вы из российских
eats and
они этот ест и
Buryats Buddhists I don’t know if
бурятов буддистам не знаю есть
you have a special Ukraine for him here we
вы украины специального на он здесь
mix a mixture of clay specially
перемешиваем смесь глины специально
chosen
выбрали
before that with the Russians then I talked with the
до этого с русскими общался потом с
Kazakhs then with the Belarusians then the
казахами потом с белорусами потом
ichor of them and me there about sit down
сукровица еще их и меня там порядка сядь
and
да
nothing in common just like that I’m sitting
ничего общего просто просто так сижу
people themselves something  they tell me and all this is
люди сами что-то мне говорят и всё это
porridge without a clue what I myself
каша без понятия о чем мне самому
should talk about my position in life is
говорить жизненная позиция
cheerful, I told you what I
веселый я вам рассказал так какая
gave you basically they say that we should
дал основном говорят что мы должны
separate from Russia until,
отделиться от россии до
well, I don’t know, maybe it
только когда ну не знаю может вам было
would be good for you, it means not an arch, I want
бы хорошо значит неарх одни хочу чтобы
there to be a civil war here  for an hour there
здесь была гражданская война на час
will be a degree why there should be a
будет градуса почему должна быть
peasant war,
крестьянская война
well, here to say basically everything will be, then
ну здесь сказать в основном все будет то
he doesn’t know his own language  so even if we
своего языка не знает как больше если
have only one here, we even have nationalism and
даже один здесь у нас даже национализм и
it won’t work if, look, the Jews
не получится коли смотрите евреи
once also didn’t know the type of konichiva, they
когда-то тоже не знали вида коничива
taught
учили
I hope that in every Buryat family there is a
надеюсь в каждой бурятской семьи бури
Russian daughter, and so I have a
русская дочь и так что у меня брат
cousin rus and here’s another
двоюродный rus и вот другой брат
cousin Mickey with Russians given  me
двоюродный микки с русскими данную меня
and a mixed marriage is not an iron essence that he
и смешанный брак не железную суть что он
doesn’t look you now have the status of a
не смотрите у вас сейчас есть статус
republic yes there was a republic and there
республики да там республика были а не
’s nothing to differ on, you will also
на чем будет это отличаться так же тоже
live mestizos ladies ladies someone’s brother
будете жить метисы дам дам кто-то брат
sister mom such a dad like that but you will be in
сестра мама такой папа такой но будет
charge  not Moscow to Alan yes there
вам и руководить не москва алану да там
or whoever the
или кто
money will remain with your
деньги будут оставаться с вашей
republic not to go to Moscow but you have it
республике не в москву идти а у вас
distributed
распределяться
over the skin also distribution to the bed but
по коже также распределение станине а от
from somewhere for a long time your money
откуда-то долго твои деньги
but in the same place where the tonalka is the same
но там же где тоналку какой то же
percentage the brain is the main one gets glad the
процент мозгу это основное получает рада
risk is better  and so on until it climbs and
риску лучше и так дальше до забирается и
some of them return, mom leaves
часть из них возвращается мам оставляет
some, well, yes, a whim, or the side
часть ну да уж прихоть или же сторона
has the right to inspect, and so you would get
вправе осмотрите а так вы бы получил
why, look, why small
почему смотрите почему маленькая
What is Iceland, which has 300,000 people, I have
исландия который 300000 человек у меня
a better standard of living than in Russia in such a
уровень жизни лучше чем в россии в такой
rich resource, why,
богатой ресурсами почему так
since we will trade for
как мы будем торговать на
our mother and we dressed, and that where should we
зосимой мать и мы оделись и что куда нам
go next by
дальше идти по
sea,
морю на
this will also pass through other countries
это также будете через другие страны
, your installation is still in  what is the
проходить вашей эти монтаже еще в чем
problem
проблема
through russia and through mongolia, well,
через россию и через монголию ну во
firstly, not through russia, because instead of
первых не через россию потому что вместо
russia there will also be the rest of the
россии будет уже тоже остальные там
republics of the whale there, well, yes, they will pass
республики кита ну да будут проходить
like in europe it goes through a bunch of countries of
как в европе проходит через кучу стран
trade,
торговли
something else, but when reading the collapse of the country, i don’t
то еще что то но читая развала страны не
want to, don’t want to, but  look it’s a
хочу ну не хотите но это смотрите это
little scary because somehow there’s
немножко страшно потому что как-то вот
an empire that was a Russian empire
есть империя была российской империи
nothing fell apart they live normally there
ничего развалилась живут нормально там
Poland Finland and it was necessary to be Soviet
польша финляндию и надо был советский
where there was so much meat when the
куда столь на столько мяса был когда
Russian empire collapsed so not meat
российской империи развалюсь так не мясо
because of which there was meat not because of  the
из-за чего было мясо не не из за того
fact that it fell apart and it just
что она развалились а она как раз и
fell apart because of these problems
развалилась из-за вот этих проблем
that have accumulated because the
которые накопились потому что кидал
first world war would have been thrown  la, that
воевал первая мировая война была так то
is, he threw all the people like meat for the sake of
есть это всех людей кидал как мясо ради
his military ambitions, so they didn’t work
своих военных амбиций так они не
out, and these are all the people, so it’s
получились и вот эти все люди так они
like they themselves became a catalyst for the
как бы сами это стало катализатором
collapse of the Russian empire, just
развала российской империи так же само
like now the current emperor Putin, he
как сейчас теперешний император путин он
throws people to war in Ukraine so  this
бросает людей на войну в украине так эта
war is already being lost by Russia and will be
война уже проигрывается россии и будет
finally lost and will lead to
окончательно проиграна и приведет к вот
such consequences
таким последствиям
dias that this meat will be regardless
диас том что это мясо будет независимо
of whether Russia will have to or
от того раз придется россии или не
will not fall apart, so if you are recruiting Dacians now you
распадется так если у вас даков сейчас
have seen this video even in films
набирают видели это видео даже в фильмах
bunnies are being recruited for a special military
зайков набирают на специальную военную
operation for a
операцию
long time  it’s time we are already collecting recycling for 6
давно пора уже набираем утилизацию на 6
6 months, he returns in the spring, then
6 месяцев он весной возвращается потом
so where will these killers and rapists
так куда эти убийцы и насильники
return with this close-knit military
вернуться с со сплоченным боевым этим
access to experiments what they do to me will be
доступ к опытам что они мне делать будет
meat then plant them with when after this is
мясо то сажать их с когда после это вот
when after the Great Patriotic War there are a
когда после великой отечественной много
lot of square meters there  fought you came there
же за кв там воевала ты приходили там
[ __ ]
сучье
history taking into account
истории с учетом
[music]
[музыка]
character
персонаж
like this
вот так
people
люди
people give out and a couple of Scythian  I specifically
люди выдавать и пару скифскую специально
say that all Russian people from Russia are already
что все русские люди из россии уже
starting to think about the
начинают задумываться о
collapse of the empire, and this is very correct,
распаде империи и это очень правильно
look four months ago when
смотрите еще четыре месяца назад когда
we raised this issue, many there in the
мы поднимали этот вопрос многие там в
chat wrote that it was
чате писали это как это
not the Soviet Union, too, when something that was painted in the
не советский союз тоже когда то что в
eighties would fall apart
восьмидесятых раскрашивают распадется
in three-  for four years everything
через три-четыре года все поскольку
is afraid because they were twisting it, and now for another
крутили боится и также сейчас еще
six months it’s cool to say that Russia has collapsed
полгода круто сказать что россия развале
so because it’s well, now they are already
так потому это ну а сейчас уже с каждого
talking about the division of Russia
утюга говорят про разделение россии так
into independent national states from every iron,
на независимые национальные государства
and the
и
Russians are also already starting to think about it
россияне тоже уже начинают об этом
and at the mine their task is
задуматься и на шахте их задача
wider  when they spread this
пошире ты когда распространяют эту
information with these thoughts people should think
информацию этим мысли люди должны думать
people should think
люди должны задумываться
justified we without Russia without the height of
оправдали мы без россии без высоты
empires will not be able what is true if we
империй не сможет что правда если мы
look back there will be a civil war what is
оглянемся будет гражданская война что
true we will not be able to trade for people
правда на не сможем торговать на людей
there are such fears it is just like
есть такие страхи это так же как
for example a person
например человек
works for
работает на
hired workers  so they tell him that
наемным работникам так и ему говорят что
you can look, for example, in your b  I’ve worn
смотри можно например в свой бизнес
out trying to start
попробовать начать
a yukata, what will be the result of the
юкату это ж надо будет какому результату
payment if we still calculate it for me
выплате если мы все равно это мне
Yes, it’s a lot of a lot of risk that
рассчитать да это куча куча риска будто
you need to do business not just
бизнесом заниматься надо не просто
take it, it came worked, it’s gone
возьмите тот пришел отработал ушел
much more difficult on the right, so I wanted the system
намного сложнее справа так хотел систему
to take responsibility absolutely
брать на себя ответственность абсолютно
here just the same from  but
тут так же само от но
while you will be subordinate to this
пока ты будешь подчиненных этому
emperor and you will not have a language
императору а у вас не языка не будете и
and will continue to have your identity so
дальше и будет идентичность вашу так
kill but you will always remain some kind of
убивать но всегда вы останетесь каким-то
second grade to some Asians so
вторым сортом до какими-то азиатами вот
you will read ads further there we
и будете читать объявления дальше там
rent an apartment only Slavs I remember a
сдаем квартиру только славян я помню
girl  there was a blogger from Buryatia somewhere in
девушка с бурятии блогер где-то в
Voronezh, she tried to rent an
воронеже было да пробовала снять
apartment, she showed what attitude to
квартиру показывала какое отношение к
people from Buryatia, that is, throwing you to
людям из бурятии то есть бросать вас
die in the coals is not an empire, but
умирать в угли не это империя может да
that you were on an equal footing with you,
что вы были на равными вам не может
why don’t you know your behind to the pillow
почему вы не знаете свою за к подушке
empire on purpose  we specifically
империя специально специально
russify peoples, removes their
русифицируем народы убирает у них
national identity
национальное самосознание
and it is very important that this national
и очень важно это национальное
identity is raised  if you think
самосознание поднимать если вы думаете
that we don’t talk about a man, is it
что мужика мы не говорим паук ли и
okay in Ukraine, too, a lot of
порядке в украине тоже очень много
cities were Russified, people
городов были русифицированы люди
came from all even Ukrainian speakers and in the
приезжали из все даже украиноязычные и в
city they began to speak Russian
городе начинали говорить по-русски
because politics was a deliberate
потому что политика была специально
attack that Ukrainian means you are
атака что украинец это значит ты
some kind of Selyuk  but the urban
какой-то селюк а вот городской
educated will still have passed it already
образованный будут еще прошло это уже
when you create a national
когда вы создадите национальное
state when the Tatars create
государство когда татары создадут
national states Bashkirs the peoples of the
национальных государств башкиры народы
Caucasus then they will start national
кавказа тогда них начнет на национальное
development why is Iceland in which a pancake is a
развитие почему исландия в которой блин
small island
маленький остров
300 thousand people cold what else is
300 тысяч населения холода какие то еще
there natural conditions such they
там природные условия такие у
have GDP on  more per capita than
них ввп на душу населения больше чем
Russia in such a rich to whom why are these
руси в такой богатой до кого почему эти
people 300 thousand and can have their own
люди 300 тысяч и могут иметь свои
states to control their fate
государства распоряжаться своей судьбой
because they want their national
так как они хотят своими национальными
traditions because they want the
традициями так как они хотят
economy holy as they sit, for example, they
экономики свято как они сидят а например
drill this or the Tatars whose ax they
бурят этом или татары которых топор они
can’t  for some reason, Buryatia has a
не смогут почему то есть у бурятии
huge territory with about  huge
огромнейшее территории с огромнейшими
resources if now some company
ресурсам если сейчас какая-то компания
will
будет
extract a natural resource there and it
добывать там природный ресурс и она
will give money to Moscow and so it
будет давать деньги в москву а так она
served Fula well, and
подавала фула ну да и
not Muscovites posed, but
не москвичи позировали а
people from Buryatia why Moscow is like vodka
люди из бурятии почему москва как водка
there is a pond that drinks blood from all the regions of
есть пруд пьет кровь из всех регионов
Russia
россии
that she conquered  sometime whom
которые она покорила когда-то которых
she deprives of her identity
она лишает своей идентичности
whom she treats as
которым она относится как к людям
third-class people, it is very clearly seen from the
третьего сорта это очень хорошо видно по
statistics of those who died in Ukraine that the
статистике погибших в украине что
largest number of deaths per
наибольшее количество погибших на душу
capita in the republics is tight or
населения это республик это туго или
Tuva is like Buryatia Dagestan but not Moscow
тыва как а бурятия дагестан но не москва
and St. Petersburg with Moscow and  peter do not want or do not
и питер с москве и питер не хотят или не
send this or the metropole but
отправляю это или the metropole а должны
some conquered people must fight,
воевать какие-то покоренные народ
so if you want for your children
поэтому если вы хотите для своих детей
so for your grandchildren great-grandchildren a
так для своих внуков правнуков
good future
хорошего будущее
worthy future you must realize
достойного будущего вы должны осознать
that you are not just some Buryats, so not
что вы не просто какие-то буряты так не
just some-  then barrels or you need to have a
просто какие-то бочки или надо вы есть
nation Ukraine also did not have
нация украина тоже не имела
statehood in the twentieth century and
государственности в двадцатом веке так и
on the paws of the Russian one  Peria chose this
на лапках российской империи выбрала это
Russian chose this right for itself now
русский выбрала на себя это право сейчас
we have independent states and
мы имеем независимые государства и
very much with huge potentials
очень сильно с огромнейшей потенциалов
which, despite all the ridicule of the Russians,
которая несмотря на все насмешки русских
was able to stop this second
так смогла остановить вот эту вторую
army of the world so if you
армию мира так если
want everything you can do Israel
захотеть все можно сделать израиль
in general in the forty-eighth year, yes, that is,
вообще в сорок восьмом году да то есть у
there are two thousand years of them, or how many there were
них две тысячи лет или сколько там не
no statehood, it gets
было государственности получает
not only that there we have a gap there for
не то что там у нас там разрыв там
three hundred years, but in statehood there was no
триста лет а в государственности не было
geek to start from whom
на geek начинать из кого
there were generally 2000 tons of years a hole to and
там вообще 2000 тонн лет дырка-то к и
created because there were national
создали потому что было национальные
ideas were retained
идеи были удержание
if I’m not mistaken in the autumn of st and who
если не ошибаюсь осени ст и которые
believed that a
считали что должна быть построена
national Jewish state should be built from the
национальное еврейское государство от
Jews, everyone is welcome and come to live, then
еврей всеми радушны и приезжайте жить-то
Israel and the united national day are a
израиль объединенный национальный день
window from the most powerful states,
окно из мощнейших государств
modernity, although the population there is a bit
современность хотя население там немного
relative to the
относительно
geography, what is around all the
география какая что вокруг все
warring slave countries there for not
враждующие там рабские страны для не
they surrendered on a steep actually to the
сдались они на крутом фактически до
place
месте
when the British  th empire, in fact, also
когда британская империя по сути тоже
cracked and
трещала пошла и
successfully Israeli medicine, for example,
успешно израильская медицина например
tab, is
tab
known all over the world, there are still a lot of
известна во всем мире еще очень много
technologies going astray, so why the Buryats
технологий сбивается так почему буряты
can’t why the Tatars can’t why the
не могу почему татары не могут почему
Bashkirs can’t, therefore, everyone who listens to us
башкиры не могут поэтому все кто нас
from the Russian Federation,
слушает из российской федерации
representatives of enslaved peoples, the
представители порабощенных народов
first thing you should  you must realize
первое что вы должны вы должны осознать
who you are, who your ancestors were and
кто вы есть кто были ваши предки и
understand who your children should be, your
понять кем должны быть ваши дети ваши
grandchildren and your right if you want them
внуки и ваше право если вы захотите
to be proud of you and your people,
чтобы они гордились вами и своим народом
then you must take
то тогда надо брать ответственность на
responsibility not be afraid, yes there will be difficulties the
себя не бояться да будут трудности
first moment, but believe that the
первый момент но поверьте что
state  which are formed on the
государство которые образуются на
territory of the collapsed Russian
территории распавшейся российской
empire will still be supported by the
империи все равно будут поддержаны
world community, the
мировым сообществом также как раз
Soviet Union just poured out supported
вылился советский союз поддерживала
Europe and Ukraine and Belarus and countries, if
европа и украины и беларуси и стран если
not Asia, and even that Russia was supported by
не азии и даже ту россию поддерживал
such bush legs, and then a
такими ножками буша и тогда и очень
lot of support programs had it later
много программ поддержки было это потом
with them  woke up again there
у них проснулась снова там
anti-western cream and
крем антизападные и
kt  oh, it won’t let you just
кто не даст вам просто
die cola, nobody needs it, and
умереть колы никому это не нужно а
moreover, you just have art that you
более того искусства у вас только что вы
yourself won’t let yourself die of hunger, but
сами себе не дадите умереть с голоду но
now
сейчас на этих ресурсах нагревается
some Kremlin friends of
какие-то кремлевские друзья
Putin’s cooperative lake
путина кооператива озеро
are heating up on these resources, you can build your state so
вы можете построить свое государство так
that you manage your own  resources, you
чтобы распоряжались своими ресурсами вы
didn’t work for the
и не работали на
wealth and prosperity of your people,
богатство и процветание вашего народа
why Putin attacked Ukraine because
почему путин напал на украину потому что
he doesn’t want to see
он не хочет видеть возле себя возле
an example of a successful country next to him, successful
россии пример успешной страны успешны
which leads to successful reforms
которые приводит успешные реформы
that were torn from empires but goes into the
которые рвалась от от империй но идет в
civilized world and goes quite
цивилизованный мир так и идет довольно
successfully because  what if people see you
успешны потому что если люди увидят с
feast with everyone, yes there,
каждым пируешь да там
the EU countries and the republics in Russia first of
странами ес и республики в россии первую
all see and say how the
очередь видят и скажут как это у
Ukrainians did it, and we live somehow
украинцев получилось а мы живем как-то
wrong with our resources, this
не так при наших ресурсов вот это он
will come out,
выйдет
so
поэтому
do not
не
hesitate to set yourself huge bit
стесняйтесь ставить себе огромные битные
goals because  for every nation the
цели потому что для каждого народа
aspiration should be the teachings of its
стремлением должно быть поучений его
nation-states if you believe
национального государств если вы верите
to your people if you are worthy of your
в свой народ если вы достойны своих
ancestors glory to ukraine glory to the people
предков слава украине слава народом
who inhabit russia I believe that you
которые населяют россии я верю что вы
can be free to come off
сможете быть свободным отрываюсь
drag it to the channel section like the
притащить она отсек канал поставьте лайк
bandage but patch the comment what do you
обовязково но патчить коментар че вы
think and get rid of his mind and even run
думает и спровадить его виду и даже бежи
it is important do not
важно его не
forget him on the sts view  correct
забывайте на стс вид правильные думки
thoughts tamish all betrayals are honored
тамыши все измены почитаются
from the head
с головы
kamus enters the head and yes I am erin
камус заходит в голову и да я эрин
pacino and keep in the body but who do not
пачино и в теле в держите но кого не
dissolve these live give glory to ukraine
распустить живут эти дай слава украине